bettingclosed.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy | bettingclosed

**Information on privacy and data processing  
**

Page updated: 24 May 2018

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy statement establishes how bettingclosed.com uses and protects the information provided by the user when using this website. The owner of the personal data protection treatment of bettingclosed is Web Inside Net of Vinci Marcello , which you can contact for any kind of information on [privacy@bettingclosed.com](mailto:privacy@bettingclosed.com).

From 25 May 2018, visitors to the European Union are protected by new legislation, known by the initials GDPR. The GDPR is primarily intended to restore control to EU citizens and residents over their personal data, and every website you visit (regardless of where the website is located in the world) after May 25, 2018 must provide you, by law, adequate control over your personal data.

We are committed to ensuring that your data is protected. You can be sure that the personal information you provide while using this website will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

If you do not agree with any changes, feel free to close your account by sending an email to [privacy@bettingclosed.com](mailto:privacy@bettingclosed.com). If you continue to use our services after the changes, it means that you agree with the new conditions.

bettingclosed.com can change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page to make sure you agree with any changes. This policy is effective from 25 May 2018.

**Consent**

* * *

bettingclosed treats your data with care. The data collected on bettingclosed are stored on computer support. At the time of registration, you accept this document and the site regulations that you undertake to comply with.  
You can refuse them or ask us to change / delete your data at any time by sending an email to [privacy@bettingclosed.com](mailto:privacy@bettingclosed.com) in the subject write remove, in the body indicate which data you want to delete / modify, changes to some data can also be made directly in the personal area under the profile heading. We inform you that the communication of data is necessary for the fulfillment of the requested services; the missed conferment, as well as the partial or inexact conferment, has the consequence to prevent the punctual delivery of the service. Please note that you can delete sensitive data associated with registration at any time by sending an email to [privacy@bettingclosed.com](mailto:privacy@bettingclosed.com) in the subject write remove, in the body indicate which data you want to delete. In the same way, at any time the account can be closed, if the cancellation of the account is requested and a subscription is activated, this will be terminated and a full refund will be made in case you are entitled otherwise there are no refunds partials for the period not used (please check [terms and conditions](https://www.bettingclosed.com/rules-vip-4) for our refund policy).

**What we collect:**

* * *

We may collect the following information:

  * **Subscription / Profile**  
During the registration process we ask our users to provide us with some information such as name, username, email address and password.  
Some other information is stored (Registration date, account confirmation date, IP used for registration and IP used to confirm your account). This information is stored to comply with the GDPR and is able to check if there is any problem with someone's account. We also collect the date of birth to ensure that you are adult, the address and the state of residence are data that we use only for tax and statistical purposes, any telephone number, optionally provided by you, is collected only for a eventual future service (type whatsapp chat), in which case the authorization will be requested in advance.
  * **Management**  
The management of the subscription you have, the order linked to your subscription, the date of purchase, the expiry date, the type of subscription you have. This information must be collected to our end to ensure the management of the subscription and to improve the quality of our support and to allow you to use some of the features reserved for registered users, both paid (access VIP section and other paid features) and free (access to personalization of the profile and visualization)
  * **Statistics**  

          We may collect the following information when you use our website:

               \- Demographic information, which is the country from which you are viewing our website  
               \- Statistical information on the pages you are viewing, using Google Analytics  
               \- Preferences and settings - for example the style preference, the time zone, the display mode of meetings, your consent (or not) for the use of cookies.

**Sending email communications**

* * *

bettingclosed could send automatic service e-mails, for example, to inform about the expiry of the subscription renewal, occasionally promoting some services, and / or products both own and third parties and any newsletters.  
It is understood that prior authorization will be required for the sending of the aforementioned emails, authorization which may be revoked at any time.

**Safety**

* * *

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure.  
In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we adopt appropriate physical, electronic and management procedures to safeguard and protect the information we collect online.

No credit card information and / or Paypal account information is stored in any way by bettingclosed.

The data are processed within the company, by collaborators and employees who have been designated as responsible and / or in charge of processing and who have received the necessary and appropriate information on the subject. In no case will your personal data be transferred to third parties without your prior authorization.

**How we use cookies**

* * *

We use cookies to personalize content and advertising to make our website relevant to you and to analyze our traffic. We also use cookies to ensure that our website is legally compliant with laws and regulations in various countries and regions of the world. For example, you may be prevented from showing links to certain sportsbooks where these companies do not have a license to operate in your country.

A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit websites.

Almost all websites use cookies. Cookies are used to help analyze web traffic, store your preferences and track the path of your visit to a website from one page to another to facilitate archiving and performance when visiting a particular site. bettingclosed uses different cookies, to view the details please visit the cookie page.
